A NEW BEGINNING - Prayer for 2017 with Prophet T.B. Joshua
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Viewers all over the world, whatever medium you are using to view us right now,
with a handshake, "Good Morning!"
I say, "Good Morning," once again.
The year 2016 is coming to an end
and we are about to enter 2017, which is a new year.
let every unfavourable situation you have been in,
end with this year, 2016!
Be it your business, be it your health
be it your career, be it your family, your marriage, just name it,
let it end with this year, 2016!
This is what we call, "New Year!"
Viewers, I am not speaking to you on my own.
I am led by the Holy Spirit to pray for you, to usher you into the New Year,
to stop satan from killing, destroying and stealing from your life.
This is why we are here.
What a God we serve!
Viewers at the command of Jesus, Peter walked on the sea.
At the command of Jesus, Blind Bartimaeus regained his sight.
JESUS is the same yesterday, today and forever in the life of His anointed ones.
with Him, all things are possible.
At His command right now, I command every unfavourable situation in your life
to cease, in the name of Jesus Christ!
in your business, your finances, your health, every unfavourable situation,
I decree, in the name of Jesus, let it end with this year, 2016 -
all unfavourable situations, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Thank you, Lord!
viewers all over the world, this is the message for you.
I want you to know that whatever situation you are in this year 2016,
it will end with it, in Jesus Christ's name!
I will be right back to usher you into the New Year!
Remain in faith; thank you.
A New Beginning Prayer For 2017 With Prophet T.B Joshua
Viewers all over the world , I am here with instructions from JESUS to you.
let us open Matthew 5:8.
Matthew 5:8
"Blessed are those pure in heart, for they will see God."
This means if we regard iniquity, sin, wrong in our heart the Lord will not hear our prayer.
If you hold a grudge against a brother, you have already grieved the Holy Spirit.
you have already grieved GOD
Viewers all over the world, this means our heart is the temple; our heart is the prayer room.
Give me your heart!
let us remove the barrier between our hearts and the Spirit of GOD
let us remove it
What could be the barrier?
Grudges, strife, outrage, bitterness, pain of the past, an unforgiving spirit, hatred.
let us remove the barrier between our hearts and the Spirit of GOD
I remove the barrier, in the name of Jesus Christ!
That barrier, be removed, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I command in the name of Jesus Christ,
all knees shall bow, all tongues shall confess, "Jesus is the Lord!"
Every barrier between your heart and the Spirit of GOD, be removed, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Be removed, in the name of Jesus Christ!
That barrier, be removed, in the name of Jesus Christ!
You barrier, be removed, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Hallelujah!
liberty in prayer can only be obtained where there is a right atmosphere
That atmosphere can be one of unity and harmony.
I command that barrier to be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Be removed, in the name of Jesus Christ!
The year 2017 - I don't know time you are in your nation, your continent -
God's time is the best.
Listen to me - the year 2017 will come with challenges.
No matter the challenges my brother listen to me.
Challenges will make you stronger.
They will not impair you but improve you.
There will be many challenges.
We don't have enough time.
I have the prophetic messages for the year 2017 here.
so many challenges, but my brother listen.
Those challenges will not impair you but improve you.
I mean, your challenges will make you stronger.
Just trust and believe.
Hear GOD say to you, "The voice of wailing shall be silenced";
Listen, "The voice of difficulty shall be silenced;
the voice of setback and hardship shall be silenced."
There will be so many challenges but you just believe!
I am sent to give you a dream.
Don't forget, Jesus is the father of dreams.
He gave a dream to Abraham, a dream to Daniel, a dream to Peter.
A new dream of breakthrough for you!
A new dream of prosperity for you, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
A new dream of good health for you, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
A new dream of breakthrough!
Viewers all over the world, I want to go on my knees.
Start your knew year on your knees, for you and your household.
begin your new year on your knees.
A new dream has come - Happy New year
There will be many challenges - economic challenges, financial challenges
but your challenges will not impair you but improve you.
your struggles will make you stronger.
The message for the New Year is here but we shall meet.
Father, I want to leave your children and usher them into a new beginning.
A new dream has come - Happy New Year!
A dream of breakthrough for you!
A dream of walking with the LORD.A new dream for you!
A new dream of prosperity for you!
A new dream of good health for you!
Spiritual uplift for you, in the name of Jesus Christ!
This is the message for you.
A new dream has come - no matter the challenges, no matter what comes!
A new dream of breakthrough for you!
A new dream of prosperity for you, good health for you, in the name of Jesus!
Thank you, Lord, in Jesus Christ's name!
Amen!
Emmanuel!
(God with us Matthew 1:23)
A NEW BEGINNING - Prayer for 2017 with Prophet T.B. Joshua